[{"answer": "No, I didn't want them to take it badly in the first place.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Do you want them to take it better?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I mean --", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Too easy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "That's what they call a home run, you know?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Of course I do.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Do you have a moral code yourself?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, you can't.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What's your litmus test?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "For a very long time, you would never have imagined being in Hollywood.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "But what are we meant to do?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "What is the reality of Hollywood excess?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Is it to not be famous too early?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Is it a lot easier, is my point, to be older and become famous?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "What I can't believe is the way you look, because we all fell in love back in Britain with fat, chubby Ricky.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "It's the I can't believe my luck that I get up in the morning, have an idea, and I can start writing that idea and it will get made at the moment, you know?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "You didn't tell me then, though, did you?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Not much at all.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I got some free -- those things in a luxury lounge once, those -- I thought those made me gag.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Hollywood smiley?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "It wasn't a vanity kick.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "What made you go on this vanity kick?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "-- \"The death of a fight-useless chubby loser with -- who never cleans his teeth and stinks.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Where would you be without that?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "I don't -- never got groupies.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Do you get more groupies now?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I think --", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "A svelte comedic auteur or as a chubby loser?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "\"Seinfeld,\" lovely show.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "History of television?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "You love Twitter, don't you?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I like it for lots of reasons.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Why do you like it so much?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, you know, as a comedian --", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What were you getting at?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Well, I thought I looked intellectual there --", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "-- you'd fit in well looking like that?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Always?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, but they shouldn't.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "How does your -- how does your atheism, which you're passionate about -- how does that play with your American audience, given that so many people in America are God-fearing people, and probably take exception to it?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Do I do that?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Yes, please.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Should we play you what Steve Carell said about you?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Oh, not in a million years, no.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Perhaps, but to actually go in front of people and --", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "But you could play a Ricky Gervais character?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "-- you're all heart, aren't you?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "He's great.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Do you like Steve Carell?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I'm assuming women.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "What, with -- romantic love?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Once?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Well, we are, really.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Why haven't you married her yet?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Oh, I'd never say never.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "How do you show your romantic side?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "There's loads of things whizzing through my head, but they're all from childhood.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "It would be professional, really -- a moment in your life, what would it be?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I just remembered one.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Steve.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Steve, isn't it?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "About 140 times.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "You appeared how many times on Johnny Carson?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Yes, Bob Hope was the most, and I was the second most.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "That has to be a record, isn't it?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "Well, Charlie Hartsock and Vance DeGeneres, who are my partners at Carousel, had this idea to kind of trace the -- trace comedy in terms of generations and -- and how it cross-pollinates and sort of look to people's inspirations.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "What was the idea?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "-- of superstar comedians, isn't it?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I don't know if it's a definitive history of comedy, but it is --", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "How are you -- how are you billing it?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "It's unique in the way in which the comedians talk about what they do.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "On what makes people laugh?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "That never happened.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "That happened between you and him?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "It's so subjective.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "Is there a stat -- when you all get together?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 779, "question": "But biggest comedian wasn't your great burning ambition as a kid, was it?", "qSentId": 778}, {"answer": "Let's talk a little break, gents.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 802, "question": "And if it's funny, then, you know?", "qSentId": 801}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 828, "question": "But you do -- do you thank God every day that these things happen?", "qSentId": 827}, {"answer": "There -- there is no Moe and Larry here.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "It's a little bit like that, isn't it?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 875, "question": "It will hide your own lack of character, right?", "qSentId": 874}, {"answer": "I would take Alan Arkin.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 880, "question": "Who -- if I could trap you both on a desert island separately and you could have one comedian with you to make you laugh for the rest of your days, who would you take?", "qSentId": 879}, {"answer": "Because he makes -- one-to-one, he makes me laugh more than anyone I've ever met.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 882, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 881}, {"answer": "He is -- he's so dry and so acerbic, he just -- I love being around the man.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 884, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 883}, {"answer": "I'd probably take Groucho.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 886, "question": "Who would you take?", "qSentId": 885}, {"answer": "It's much, much better to be rich and famous.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "If you're honest, did you prefer life before, when you were more anonymous, or have you actually embraced the whole fame thing with great enthusiasm?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "It's a lot tougher to deal with, I think, if you get that kind of thing when you're younger.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "I like to think it might have been, but you never know, you know?", "qSentId": 916}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 966, "question": "Do you miss the character?", "qSentId": 965}, {"answer": "Oh, not in a million years.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 970, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "qSentId": 969}, {"answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 973, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 972}, {"answer": "And I'm writing a symphony and I have a cooking show coming up.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 991, "question": "You've got seven movies on the go, is that right, over the next two years?", "qSentId": 990}, {"answer": "Did you ever imagine here you'd be in Hollywood in your smart power suit, in the middle of a seven movie extravaganza --", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 994, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 993}, {"answer": "A billion dollars.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 997, "question": "-- earning you, potentially, a billion dollars?", "qSentId": 996}, {"answer": "I'm always pinching myself.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 1002, "question": "You must pinch yourself a bit, don't you?", "qSentId": 1001}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120304pmt", "aSentId": 1028, "question": "You need to have had cigarettes burned on you for years, don't you, to be genuinely -- to make an audience laugh?", "qSentId": 1027}]